export const Quiz1 = {
    topic: "Javascript",
    level: "Beginner",
    totalQuestions: 10,
    perQuestionScore: 1,
    questions: [
      {
        question: "We should keep our savings with banks because?",
        choices: [
          "It is safe",
          "Earns interest",
          "Can be withdrawn anytime",
          "All of the above"
        ],
        type: "MCQs",
        correctAnswer: "All of the above"
      },
      {
        question: "ATM password to be shared only with",
        choices: [
          "Spouse",
          "Obedient son",
          "Obedient daughter",
          "None of the above"
        ],
        type: "MCQs",
        correctAnswer: "None of the above"
      },
      {
        question: "KYC means",
        choices: [
          "Know your customer",
          "Know your character",
          "Both of the above",
          "None of the above"
        ],
        type: "MCQs",
        correctAnswer: "Know your customer"
      },
      {
        question: "Loans from money lenders are ",
        choices: [
          "With high rate of interest",
          "With no proper accounting",
          "With no transparency",
          "All of the above"
        ],
        type: "MCQs",
        correctAnswer: "All of the above"
      },
      {
        question: "Life insurance means ",
        choices: [
          "Insurance of human",
          "Insurance of life of human and cattle",
          "Insurance of life of machines",
          "All of the above"
        ],
        type: "MCQs",
        correctAnswer: "Insurance of human"
      },
      {
        question: "General insurance relates to insurance against",
        choices: ["Fire", "Theft", "Burglary", "All of the above"],
        type: "MCQs",
        correctAnswer: "All of the above"
      },
      {
        question: "Bank provides loan for",
        choices: ["Home", "Car", "Education", "All of the above"],
        type: "MCQs",
        correctAnswer: "All of the above"
      },
      {
        question: "Which currency note has security thread",
        choices: ["Rs.50/-", "Rs.100/-", "Rs.500/-", "All of the above"],
        type: "MCQs",
        correctAnswer: "All of the above"
      },
      {
        question: "The safest place for keeping money",
        choices: [
          "A pit dug in the ground",
          "An iron box",
          "Bank",
          "Money Lender"
        ],
        type: "MCQs",
        correctAnswer: "Bank"
      },
      {
        question: "Banks pay interest on",
        choices: ["Deposits", "Loans", "Both of the above", "None of the above"],
        type: "MCQs",
        correctAnswer: "Deposits"
      }
    ]
  };
  